ANS Record Group 2: Curatorial, 1858-ongoing
ANS Archives
- Series 15: Alan M. Stahl curator correspondence and other material, 1914-2000, bulk 1982-2000; 13 cubic feet (13 boxes)
  - Box 9 of 13
    - Standing committees – General, 1975-2000
    - CC:Mail (email program), 1997
    - ANS Alumni Association, 1997-1998
    - Medal Committee, 1976-2000
    - NotaBene, 1989-1993
    - Committee on Medieval and Early Modern Coins, 1976-2000
    - Ralph Sonnenschein, 1993-1999
    - Zvi Griliches, 1999
    - Daniel Friedenberg, 1999
    - Salzburg gift, 1996
    - NYNC (New York Numismatic Club), 1991-1999
    - NYNC (New York Numismatic Club) – History, 1990-1991
    - Loans in, 1995, 2000
    - Loans out, 1996-2000
    - Medallic sculpture – AMSA – Proposal for a supplement in the Numismatist, 1995
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) – Insurance, 1995
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) – By-laws
    - Trout Run – Medallic sculpture camp, 1996-1999
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society) – Contacts, 1993
    - Mashiko – New Ideas in Medallic Sculpture, 1992-1999
  - Box 10 of 13
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – General, 1990-1999
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1999
    - AHA (American Historical Association), 1986
    - AFA (American Française d’Archeologie Merovingienne), 1989
    - AARHMS (American Academy of Research Historians of Medieval Spain), 1980-1996
    - Coin Clubs, 1991
    - Coin Clubs, 1992
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Membership, 1996-1999
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society), 1998-2000
    - Inquires, 2000
    - Ronald Edward Zupko, 1992
    - Orestes H. Zervos, 1991-1996
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1992
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – All rejected, 1992
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – All accepted, 1992
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Insurance, 1992
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), Disposition of Medals forms, 1993
    - Coin inquiries, 1991
    - Medals inquiries, 1991
    - Decorations inquiries, 1989
    - Coin inquiries, 1989
    - Medals inquiries, 1989
    - Medals inquiries, 1988
    - Coin inquiries, 1988
    - Decorations inquiries, 1987
    - Decorations inquiries, 1992
    - Medieval information, 1982
    - Decorations information, 1981
    - Coin information, 1981
    - Medals information, 1980
    - Coin information, 1980
    - Decorations information, 1980
    - Medals inquiries, 1992
    - Coin inquiries, 1992
    - Coin inquiries, 1984
    - Medals information, 1983
    - Decorations information, 1983
    - Medieval information, 1983
    - Medals information, 1981
    - Decorations information, 1982
    - Medals information, 1982
    - Medals inquiries, 1985
    - Medals inquiries, 1984
    - Decorations inquiries, 1984
  - Box 11 of 13
    - Medals inquiries, 1986
    - Decorations inquiries, 1986
    - Coin inquiries, 1986
    - Coin inquiries, 1985
    - Decorations inquiries, 1985
    - Coin inquiries, 1987
    - Medals inquiries, 1987
    - NI (Numismatics International) – Bulletin, 1982
    - Philip Grierson collection - 1965.287 – Photographs
    - Cervera collection – Inventory, 1957
    - HSA
    - Jay M. Galst exhibit, 1990
    - M. Philippe Suret-Canale, 1988
    - Seltman collection (now dispersed) from John Slocum, 1974
    - Various collections
    - Changarnier collection – Jean Guerlay, 1931
    - Drafts, 1984
    - Crusader correspondence, 1980-1986
    - Crusader exhibit, 1991
    - Deniers tournois, 1984-1986
    - Photographs from B.N. Ablaincourt
    - Carolingian photographs and plans
    - Carolingian – Henry Grunthal
    - Ablaincourt, 1982-1988
    - Medieval Spanish – Notes and photographs from George Miles relating to HAS
    - Hungarian hoard, 1970
    - Oberlauterbach hoard, 1981-1982
    - Crusader hoards – George Miles, 1966
    - Gold fragments, 1992
    - J.P. Morgan collection, 1919-1996
    - Carrara medals, 1994
    - J. Sanford Saltus Medal Award winners, 1980
    - Indian Peace Medals, 1987-1999
    - Indian Peace Medals, ANS collections (early material mostly photocopies, with one original), 1917-1994
    - Indian Peace Medals, ANS collections (early material mostly photocopies, with one original), 1917-1994
    - Indian Peace Medals – Treaty of Green Ville, 1986-1994
    - American Revolution Medals, 1995-1996
    - Columbus exhibit labels
    - Texts – Medals, 1997-1998
    - Jiri Harcuba - J. Sanford Saltus Medal Award winner (1988), 1988-1990
    - Trish Halpin, 1996
    - Victor David Brenner – Biographical materials including National Archives, 1999
    - John André Medal, 1998
    - Robert W. Hoge, 1982-1993
    - Dan Hopkins, 1998
    - Neil Harris – The Numismatist, 1983
    - Peter Ilisch, 1994-1996
  - Box 12 of 13
    - Miguel Ibanez Artica, 1996
    - Dora DePedery-Hunt, 1984-1987
    - David Jacoby, 1986-1996
    - Martin Jacobowitz, 1995
    - Vujadin Ivanisevic, 1991
    - Robert T. Ingoglia, 1988-1993
    - Martha C. Jenks, 1998
    - Edward A. Jencius, 1989
    - Virginia Janssen, 1999
    - Dick Johnson, 1977-1986
    - Elizabeth Jones, 1989-1996
    - Samuel Johnson, 1995
    - Mariangela Johnson, 1990
    - Reinhold Jordan, 1982-1988
    - Mark Jones, 1982-1994
    - Bernd Kluge, 1985
    - Ulrich Klein, 1986-1997
    - Ranee Katzenstein, 1985-1988
    - Ruth Mazo Karras, 1984-1994
    - Barbara Kreutz, 1990
    - Gregor A. Kalas, 1995-1996
    - Robert W. Julian, 1996
    - Genevra Kornbluth, 1985-1987
    - Rachel Koopmans, 1996-1997
    - Benjamin G. Kohl, 1993-1996
    - Franz Koenig project – Geneva, 1986-1987
    - Ron Landis – Gallery Mint Museum – Dollar coin design, 1995
    - Jean Lafaurie, 1980-1997
    - M. Jacques Labrot, 1990
    - Patricia H. Labalme, 1996-1998
    - Andrew Kurt, 1996
    - Quincentenary medal – Rejects, 1991
    - Quincentenary – Mistake, 1991-1992
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1990
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1988
    - ANS Endowment Medal, 1988
    - M. Crusafont i Sabater and Anna M. Balaguer, 1984-1995
    - Florin Curta, 1996-1999
    - George S. Cuhaj, 1988-1995
    - Jasminka de Luigi, 1996
    - William R. Day, 1993-1999
    - John Day, 1993
    - John Dotson, 1991-1996
    - Windsor Medal, 1997
    - Inquiries, 1999
    - East Hall exhibit – American Numismatic Design, 1892-1922
    - Medieval Academy of America meeting, 1998
    - Medieval Institute – Kalamazoo, 1998
    - Summer Seminar, 1999
    - Augustus Saint-Gaudens – French loan, 1998-1999
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1997
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference) – Public relations, 1997
    - Torneselli research, 1982
    - Torneselli research – Form letter, 1982
    - Torneselli research – Correspondence, 1980-1982
    - Torneselli research – Reviews, 1986-1991
    - Torneselli research – Notes
    - Torneselli research – ANS text, 1983
    - Torneselli research – Hoard #2
    - Torneselli research – Hoard #3
    - Columbia University Seminar text – Mint of Venice and its Capitularies, 1984
    - Kalamazoo text – Venice’s Coinage for Greece, 1982
    - British Museum, 1982-1988
    - Keiichi Uryu - J. Sanford Saltus Medal Award winner (1989), 1983-1990
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1996
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1995
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society), 1995
  - Box 13 of 13
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1998
    - ANS Endowment Medal competition, 1988-1989
    - ANS Endowment Medal competition (binder), 1988-1989
    - ANS Endowment Medal competition – Information packet, 1988
    - ANS Endowment Medal, 1988
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Catalogs, 1990, 1994
    - Texts of papers, 1996
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1997
    - COAC - John Adams, 1998
    - COAC - Ron Landis
    - COAC - Virginia Janssen, 1998
    - COAC - Bob Mueller, 1997
    - COAC - Susan Luftschein
    - COAC - Barbara A. Baxter, 1998
    - COAC - Thayer Tolles
    - COAC - Paul Rich and Guillermo De Los Reyes, 1999
    - COAC - Scott Miller, 1999
    - COAC – Chris Neuzil, 1998
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1996
    - Columbus Quincentennial medal – Magdalena Dobrucka – Production, 1992
    - Statue of Liberty medal – Production, 1985-1986
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1996
    - Correspondence – Scholars – Medals, A-M
    - Correspondence - Scholars – Medals, O-Z
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Sculpture photographs and drawings, 1996-2000, and postcard from J.S.S. to Bauman Belden, 1914
- Series 15: Carmen Arnold-Biucchi curator correspondence, 1982-1999; 2 cubic feet (2 boxes)
  Arnold-Biucchi, Carmen; Correspondence
  Contains correspondence mostly generated in response to inquiries from scholars and the general public, discussing the details and attribution of specific coins, the processing of photograph orders, and the numismatic profession in general. Includes responses to individual children and school groups interested in coin collecting. In addition to the files of general correspondence, there several on specific topics, such as Richard Giedroyc’s research on coins from the Pontus region (1985) and donations made by him to ANS (1991); Harry W. Fowler Memorial Lectures featuring Frank Lee Holt and Michel Amandry (1998-1999); a possible donation of ancient coins from Joel B. Handshu (1996); Arnold-Biucchi’s identification of a coin that had been stolen from the Kabul Museum (1999); and the review of ANS policies and procedures relating to the acquisition of foreign coins, an undertaking influenced by a UNESCO convention on the Means of Prohibiting the Illegal Import, Export, and Transfer of Cultural Property (1988-1989).
  Carmen Arnold-Biucchi joined the ANS staff as a Greek and Roman curatorial assistant in 1982 before becoming assistant curator of ancient coins (1984-1989) and the first Margaret Thompson Curator of Greek Coins (1989-2000). A graduate of the University of Fribourg (M.A., 1971; Ph.D., 1976), she was employed by the Lexicon Iconographicum Mythologiae Classicae (LIMC) in Basle (1974-1977) and at Rutgers University in New Jersey (1979-1981) before her employment at ANS, which followed her attendance of the ANS Graduate Summer Seminar in 1981. She currently holds the position of Damarete Curator of Ancient Coins, Division of Asian and Mediterranean Art, Harvard Art Museums.
  - Box 1 of 2
    - 1982
    - 1983
    - 1984
    - 1985
    - 1986
    - 1987
    - 1988
    - 1989
    - 1990 A-G
    - 1990 H-Z
    - 1991 A-L
    - 1991 M-Z
    - 1992 A-K
    - 1992 L-Z
  - Box 2 of 2
    - 1993-1994 A-E
    - 1993-1994 F-K
    - 1993-1994 L-R
    - 1993-1994 S-Z
    - 1995 A-K
    - 1995 L-Z
    - 1997-1999 A-D
    - 1997-1999 E-M
    - 1997-1999 N-Z
    - Richard Giedroyc, 1985-1991
    - Acquisitions: policy, procedure, forms, 1988-1989
    - Handshu collection, 1996
    - H.W. Fowler Lecture, 1998-1999
    - Ben Damsky, 1998-1999
    - Silver to move to Roman collection
    - UNESCO – Stolen antiquities, 1999
- Series 16: Rose Chan Houston curator correspondence, 1947-1988; 0.5 cubic feet (1 box)
  Houston, Rose Chan; Wang, Yu-ch'uan; Correspondence; Reports
  Rose Chan Houston of Bronxville, N.Y., obtained her B.A. from Marion College, Indianapolis, in 1959, before attending Fordham University, obtaining an M.A. in Modern European and American History in 1961 and a Ph.D. in Modern Diplomatic History in 1971. She joined the ANS in 1971 where she served as assistant (1971-1973) and associate (1973-1988) curator of Far Eastern coins. In the summer of 1988 the Far Eastern curatorship was eliminated because of financial constraints. Prior to her time at ANS, Chan had been a librarian at Fordham University (1961-1966) and an instructor of history at Yeshiva University (1968-1969). In later years she again worked as a librarian at the School of the Holy Child in Rye, New York. Her articles on Chinese coins and other topics appeared in such publications as Museum Notes and International Bank Note Society Journal.
  Contains official correspondence and some other records relating to Rose Chan Houston’s work as assistant (1971-1973) and associate (1973-1988) curator of Far Eastern coins at the American Numismatic Society. Letters include discussions with scholars, the general public, and representatives of museums and similar institutions, much of which has to do with the identification and the attribution of coins. Also discussed are matters pertaining to ANS collections, including the donation of a collection of Korean coins by the wife of E.J. Mandel (1978.252 – in Correspondence – General, 1), the Neil Gordon Munro portion of the John Reilly Jr. collection (Correspondence – General, 3), the Li collection (1987.19), the Sydney Rothstein collection (1978-1987), Chin Lin Yao coins (1987.94), the sale of duplicates (1974-1981, 1988, includes photographs), and coins placed in bank vaults for security (1988). Various other topics, such as visitors seeking vault privileges, Houston’s review of drafts of numismatic papers, and matters pertaining to her own publishing efforts, are also discussed. In addition, there are photographs and labels with text from an exhibit on Chinese coins, and minutes and correspondence with standing committees on East Asian and Far Eastern coins (1976-1988). The earliest materials, which pre-date Houston’s time at ANS, have to do with efforts to arrange for the study of the ANS’s collection of Chinese coins, and include the progress reports (1947) from Yü-ch'üan Wang, author of the ANS publication Early Chinese Coinage (1951), and materials regarding later efforts to carry on the work, such as grant applications resulting in the appointment of researcher Chee-Nam Tay (1968).
  - Box 1 of 1
    - Correspondence – General, 1971-1987 (3 folders)
    - Correspondence – Identification, 1971-1976
    - Correspondence – Identification, 1976-1980
    - Correspondence – Identification, 1980-1984
    - Correspondence – Identification, 1984-1988
    - Standing Committee on East Asian Coins, 1976-1988
    - Standing Committee on Far Eastern Coins, 1976-1988
    - Exhibit photographs and labels, no date
    - Coins placed in bank vault, 1988
    - Daniel Cruson – Notes on manuscript, 1982
    - Sydney Rothstein collection, 1978-1987
    - Chin Lin Yao (1987.94)
    - Li collection (1987.19)
    - Coin purchases by mail, 1974-1986
    - Sale of duplicates, 1974-1981
    - Joseph E. Boling – Appraisal for disposition of material, 1988
    - Japanese notes – Sale of duplicates, 1988
    - New-York Historical Society – Counterstamped dollar loan, 1983-1984
    - Essex Institute and Peabody Museum – Chinese paper currency – Davis collection, 1975
    - Ellen E. Morrison- Paper proposal, 1966
    - Chinese collection project – Chee-Nam Tay, 1966-1967
    - Yü-ch'üan Wang – Reports on the progress of the study for Chinese coins, 1947
- Series 17: William L. Bischoff curator correspondence, 1987; 0.5 cubic feet (1 box)
  Bischoff, William L. (William Ludwig), 1938-; Correspondence
  William L. Bischoff (1938-2010) was assistant (January 1987-October 1988) and associate (October 1988-May 1989) curator of modern coins at the American Numismatic Society. He was born in Dallas, Texas, and grew up in Fresno, California. He attended Stanford (B.A., 1960) and Harvard (Ph.D., 1970) Universities and then went on to hold an assistant professorship at the Universidad de las Americas in Puebla, Mexico (1970-1972), work as director of a prison education program for the Law Enforcement Assistance Administration and the University of Massachusetts in Boston (1973-1974), and teach as an associate professor of Bard College at Simon’s Rock in Great Barrington, Massachusetts. After leaving the ANS, he became curator of numismatics at the Newark Museum (1991-1997).
  Correspondence having to do with inquiries from the general public regarding the hobby of coin collecting and the value and identification of coins, among other topics.
  - Inquiries, January 1987
  - Inquiries, February 1987
  - Inquiries, March 1987
  - Inquiries, April 1987
  - Inquiries, May 1987
  - Inquiries, June 1987
  - Inquiries, July 1987
  - Inquiries, August 1987
  - Inquiries, September 1987
  - Inquiries, October 1987
  - Inquiries, November 1987
  - Inquiries, December 1987
- Series 18: William E. Metcalf curator correspondence, 1954-2000, bulk 1982-2000; 10 cubic feet (10 boxes)
  Though some patterns can be discerned, the materials are unarranged. This disorder may have been the result of the packing and unpacking of the records during one of the Society’s physical relocations that took place after Metcalf’s departure.
  Metcalf, William E., 1947-; Correspondence; Memorandums
  William E. Metcalf (b. 1947) served the American Numismatic Society as assistant (1973-1975), associate (1975-1978), and curator (1978-2000) of Roman and Byzantine coins. In addition, he held the positions of deputy chief curator (1978 -1979) and chief curator (1979-2000). Majoring in classical studies, he received his bachelor’s (1969), master’s (1970), and doctorate degrees (1973) at the University of Michigan. After leaving the ANS, Metcalf became an associate professor at New York University (2000-2002) and then professor of classics and curator of coins and medals at Yale University Art Gallery (2002-).
  Contains official correspondence relating to Metcalf’s role as ANS curator and chief curator, including letters filed by year (1982-1999) on topics such as inquiries from the general public about coins and numismatics; the fulfilling of orders for casts and photographs of ANS collections; the arranging of lecturers and students for the Summer Seminar; letters of support from Metcalf for individuals or projects; the arranging of his own lectures; and gifts of coins, books, and money. Also present are staff memorandums on various ANS policies and procedures sent by Metcalf as chief curator, some of which were circulated and initialed by staff (1982-1999); materials relating to the activities of a five-year plan and long-range planning committee, which includes a detailed memorandum from Metcalf addressing problems relating to the Society’s Audubon Terrace location and raising the possibility of the Society’s relocation (1991-1993); correspondence between Phil Mossman and Leslie Elam about James C. Spilman’s desire to divest himself of responsibility for the CNL (Colonial Newsletter) Foundation (1995-1996); general information for seminar students, including assessments of the restaurants in Washington Heights (William E. Metcalf, 1988, Box 7); a letter to John J. Pittman concerning the Bechtler press (P, 1986-1989, Box 7); correspondence pertaining to the sale by Johns Hopkins University of the John Work Garrett coin collection (Evergreen House, 1978-1979, Box 2); materials relating to the Juan Suros and William Sheldon ANS coin thefts (Box 2); and items relating to an insurance claim for coins said to be stolen but that may have in fact been in the possession of the ANS (Travelers Company, 1988). Also includes some files that Metcalf may have been using for research, such as the earliest materials found in these records: correspondence, notes, and photographs relating to several hoards (1954-, Box 3), and letters and notes from Alexander Veglery to George Miles on Byzantine seals (1963).
  - Box 1 of 10
    - Memorandums, 1982-1986
    - Memorandums, 1987-1988
    - Memorandums, 1989-1990
    - Memorandums, 1991-1992
    - Memorandums, 1993-1994
    - Memorandums, 1994-1997
    - Memorandums, 1995-1998
    - Memorandums, 1998
    - Memorandums, 1999
    - Memorandums, 2000
    - Library procedures, 1982-1988
    - Curatorial policies and procedures, 1990, 1993
    - Goals, 1985
    - Five-year committee – Long range planning committee, 1991-1992
    - Long range planning committee – Jack Kroll, 1993
    - Digest of council minutes and section drafts for planned ANS history from 1958 to 1982
    - Correspondence – Various – Includes procedures, item disposition, and thefts, e.g., Clapp, Naftzger, Breen, Suros, 1990-1991
    - INC (International Numismatic Congress) – Computerization, 1990-1991
    - AJN (American Journal of Numismatics), 1988-1990
    - Carmen Arnold-Biucchi, 1989
    - T.R. Martin – Paper for Waggoner memorial colloquium, 1990-1991
    - Nancy M. Waggoner colloquium, 1989-1991
  - Box 2 of 10
    - ANS miscellaneous, 1988-1989
    - Margret S. Pond Rothman, 1988
    - Ad Hoc Committee, 1985
    - Evergreen House—Garrett collection—Johns Hopkins, 1978-1979
    - Leslie Cornell, 1984-1985
    - Caesarea-Commodos Notes, 1986-1989
    - Bill Metcalf, 1988-1989
    - Columbia Seminar, 1986
    - A.H. Baldwin & Sons, 1992-1993 (1993.8)
    - Frank Berger, 1993
    - Ellen Bauerle, 1993
    - Margaret A. Brucia, 1992
    - Glen W. Bowersock, 1992
    - Erik Christiansen, 1992
    - Edward and Betsy Cohen, 1997-1998
    - R.P. Duncan Jones, 1992-1993
    - Katharina Eldada, 1993
    - Peter R. Franke, 1995
    - Franks, 1992
    - M. Paz Garcia-Bellido, 1992-1995
    - Robert Göbl, 1993
    - John H. Humphrey, 1992
    - A.E.M. Johnston, 1996-1998
    - Peter Kos, 1992
    - Georges Le Rider, 1993
    - McGill University, 1992
    - Bernhard H. Overbeck, 1993
    - Abstraction—Suros theft, 1989
    - Juan Suros donations and theft, 1989
    - Juan Suros
    - Stolen—List of merchandise stolen from Ed Hipps Sr., 2000
    - Large Cents—Theft—Sheldon—Clapp—1, 1990-1993
    - Large Cents—Theft—Sheldon—Clapp—2, 1996-1998
    - Large Cents—Theft—Sheldon—Clapp—3, 1991-1993
    - Large Cents—Theft—Sheldon—Clapp—4, 1991-1996
    - Large Cents—Theft—Sheldon—Clapp—5, 1996-1997
  - Box 3 of 10
    - Coin photographs (1 of 2)
    - Coin photographs (2 of 2)
    - SIGLOS (San Francisco Ancient Numismatic Society)
    - Intelligibility of Roman Types
    - Cervera collection—Bellido (1 of 2), 1992
    - Cervera collection—Bellido (2 of 2), 1992
    - Gloria Mora—El Coleccionismo Numismatico en España
    - NMA (National Museum Act) grant—metal analysis, 1977-1998
    - Chalifoux – Coin photographs
    - Ostia – Representative types of hoard found at Ostia (NSC, 1950, pp. 326-331) – Photo order, 5294
    - Byzantine seals – George Miles, 1963
    - Electrotypes – British Museum – Jessie D. Newby
    - Tell-Kalak hoard—Letter and rubbings, 1954
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1966
    - Aiello’s Alexander Hoard, 1992
    - Collection of the State Historical Society, Madison, Wisconsin—Photos, 1957
    - Gerzeul Hoard
    - Disposition of duplicates, 1975
    - Analyses of Alexandrian 4DR
    - Ancona
    - Hoard—Turkey—Late Roman Silver folles, 1970s
    - Ashmunein Hoard—George Miles notes, 1954
    - Donner’s Eastern hoard
    - DiLauro’s Alexandrian hoard, 1979
    - Wulfing collection
    - Haifa hoard, 1975
    - Ben Damsky, 1994-1998
    - P.K. Anderson collection, 1969 (69.222)
    - Wilbert C. When—Eugene Miles collection, 1971 (69.83)
    - Capalbio hoard, 1954-1986
    - J. Nollé, 1995
  - Box 4 of 10
    - Fundraising—Includes prospect profiles on Damsky, Beleson, Bormann, Harlick, 1993
    - Development committee—Prospects, 1986
    - Fellow Nominations, 1993-1994
    - Talks—Money of Alexander, Greek coins of history
    - ANS chief curator—Job description, photo file policies, Brady, etc., 1978-1979
    - Curatorial data, 1968-1979
    - Page proofs—New Hoard of Posthumous Alexanders, 1994
    - Patricia J. Singer, 1988
    - Axel Jürging, 1995
    - Coins database, 1995
    - ANS computer manual, 1994
    - Otho, 1991
    - American Journal of Archaeology, 1988-1995